(Penny:)I want to believe you.
I really do.
(Penny:)Am I being naive?
(Bernadette:)Oh, I don't know.
(Bernadette:)This is all so new to me.
(Bernadette:)I'm still processing.
(Penny:)You know, he never would've
done this when we first met.
(Penny:)He's cockier now.
(Amy:)That's because you made him
more confident.
(Bernadette:)You know, if you think about it,
without you,
(Bernadette:)he never would've grown
into the person he is now.
(Bernadette:)I mean, sure,
more women might notice him,
(Bernadette:)but I think it's better
to have a guy be with you
(Bernadette:)because he wants to be
(Bernadette:)and not because he thinks he
doesn't have any other choice.
(Penny:)I never thought
about it like that.
(Bernadette:)Oh, me neither,
not until just now.
Hello. I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper,
and welcome to "Sheldon Cooper
Presents: Fun With Flags."
You may notice that
I'm holding a remote control.
That's because my cameraperson
and co-host,
Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler,
has chosen to end
her relationship with me.
I'm going to pause here
to let that sink in.